Asia Hamdi Mubarak Adam

GIS Specialist & Geospatial Data Analyst

Email: asia231999@gmail.com | Phone: 00201060499537 | Location: Giza, Egypt

Professional Summary

GIS Specialist and Geospatial Data Analyst with extensive experience in geospatial data analysis, remote sensing, and GIS applications. Proficient in QGIS, ArcGIS, Google Earth Engine. Strong background in environmental analysis and flood mapping, with a Bachelor's degree in Geographic Information System & Remote Sensing from Future University.

Education

Master's in Geographic Information System & Remote Sensing

Khartoum University

Field of Study: Geographic Information System

Status: Under Registration

B.Sc. (Honors) in Geographic Information System

Future University, Khartoum, Sudan Duration: October 2015 - July 2019

Faculty: Geoinformatics

Experience

Telecommunication and Post Regulatory Authority - Sudan

GIS Training (Feb 2020)

Remote Sensing Center

Training (March 2019 - May 2019)

Sudan Currency Printing Press

National Service Recruit in Computer Maintenance Department (June 2021 - 2022)

Online Instructor

Taught online classes in Google Earth Engine

Freelancer

Providing consulting services as a GIS specialist and remote sensing expert

Courses

- Geomatics academy: Design of Flood Protection and Storm Drain Works
- UDACIY: Full Stack Development Track

ESRI: Geo App

ESRI: GIS for Climate Action

ESRI: Going Places with Spatial Analysis

• Solo Learn: Intro to HTML

• Solo Learn: Intro to CSS

ESRI: Imagery in Action

Edraak: Internet and Email Essentials

New Horizon: Introduction to Web Development Using SQL & PHP

Solo Learn: Intro to JavaScript

• Geo Steps Academy: Python in GIs

Geo University: QGIS 3 Desktop

• ESRI: The Location Advantage

ESRI: ArcGIS Pro Basics

New Horizon: Basic Adobe Premiere

• ESRI: Basics of JavaScript Web Apps

EARI: Cartography

Edraak: Computer Essentials

Coursera: Python for Everyone

Skills

- Geospatial Analysis: Environmental analysis, flood mapping, remote sensing applications.
- Software Proficiency: QGIS, ArcGIS, Google Earth Engine, ENVI, ERDAS, Microsoft Office.
- Programming Languages: Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.
- Interpersonal Skills: Excellent communication, quick learner, strong analytical abilities.